<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Designs on Darius Wieczorek    DEL-ART</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/</link><description>Recent content in Designs on Darius Wieczorek    DEL-ART</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://del-art.ca/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Promotional materials</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/ts_promo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/ts_promo/</guid><description>&lt;p>Low-budget projects implemented for the needs of current and annual events. Usually prepared on the basis of provided amateur-quality photographs and low-resolution references of sponsors' corporate materials.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Promotional materials' graphic design for public events includes: posters, flyers, invitations, press ads, tickets, event programs, social media banners, and any advertisement that may be applicable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Flagship Gallery Marketing Collaterals</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/flagship_collaterals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/flagship_collaterals/</guid><description>&lt;p>Flagship Gallery uses visual content in print and digital media&amp;hellip;
The gallery hosts recurring monthly events, for which I have developed digital and physical content; published on the gallery&amp;rsquo;s website, social media accounts, as well as on printed posters and flyers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Logo design</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/logos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/logos/</guid><description>&lt;p>Gallery X logo is actually refining of the originally proposed design. The alternative developments are included in the final proposition as subtle polishes, rectified character, and hints and motions of additional meaning.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Presentation's Backgrounds and Elements</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/design6_ppt_bg/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/design6_ppt_bg/</guid><description>&lt;p>PowerPoint is a leading presentation tool for most companies. It is great when it is used like any other marketing tool according to branding developed for the business.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Social Media</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/social_media/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/social_media/</guid><description>&lt;p>The ever-evolving social media domain is an important means of promotion and publicity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Banners designed for various Social Media. Advertising materials developed for simultaneous use on many platforms in promoting current events.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Web Icons design</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/design5_icons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/design5_icons/</guid><description>&lt;p>Projects executed for Cabbagetown Regent Park Community Museum were the opportunity to exercise publishing works in many media. One of the projects was renewing and updating the museum&amp;rsquo;s website.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Website Design</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/web_design/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/web_design/</guid><description>&lt;p>Website designed and developed for the online store. All visuals for the WordPress, WooCommerce site are created from scratch.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Zrodlo - Polish Folk Song and Dance Ensemble</title><link>https://del-art.ca/design/community_ensamble_marketing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://del-art.ca/design/community_ensamble_marketing/</guid><description>&lt;p>The set of promotional materials including flyers, invitations, posters, banners, tickets for the anniversary Gala. Flyers were designed as double language in a double-sided layout. The designing work was followed by print supervision in the offset print shop where the large-volume print of flyers and invitations was performed.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>