<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Darius Wieczorek    DEL-ART</title>
    <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Darius Wieczorek    DEL-ART</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://del-art.ca/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawings</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/drawings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/drawings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Drawing for me is the analytical part of creative work, it is a record of the process of thoughts. The sketchiness of the drawing is not a bad feature. As the art is not a higher level of a craft, the photographic feature of the image is not paramount to the drawing study or a picture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/painting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My painting is usually executed in oil or acrylic, and painting sketches in watercolor or temper (acrylic temper). As my biggest interest is in visual perception, I lean towards impressionist, post-impressionist, but generally, realistic art, though I am very inspired by the subjective, individualistic, and expressionistic approach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Society of Canadian Artists Exhibition Catalogue</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/sca_catalog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/sca_catalog/</guid>
      <description>Publication created in close cooperation with the organization where many artists deliver feedback and share their experience. At the end of a day all is taken into consideration in the design process that brings nice outcome and mutual satisfaction. Catalogue designed as a follow up to previous edition, preserving the format and the general composition of content. Basic technical challeng is to reproduce submitted artworks, that are RGB pictures, converted to CMYK using the proper color managment profile, to be printed in offset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promotional materials</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/ts_promo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/ts_promo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Promotional materials&amp;rsquo; graphic design for public events includes: posters, flyers, invitations, press ads, tickets, event programs, social media banners, and any advertisement that may be applicable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand and Product Promotion, Astellas</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/brand_promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/brand_promotion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Projects created and supervised for Astellas covered many areas of marketing, from the current preparation and technical supervision of infomercial publications to long-term advertising campaigns developed for periods of years. I was lucky to participate in projects following the merger of Yamanouchi and Fujisawa pharmaceutical companies that created Astellas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logo design</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/logos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/logos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gallery X logo is actually refining of the originally proposed design. The alternative developments are included in the final proposition as subtle polishes, rectified character, and hints and motions of additional meaning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmaceutical editorial materials</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/editorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/editorials/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The set of current ads and infomercials prepared for print by any publisher indicated by the customer, for various media, in various formats. As an art director, I have tailored these ads to the specifications of the publishers selected by the marketing department of the pharmaceutical companies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polly of Bridgewater Farm</title>
      <link>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/polly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://del-art.ca/portfolio/polly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The work on publishing this book was extremely fast and intense. At the same time, my wife and I worked on the general publishing concept, we designed the layout of the pages, the cover, selected the illustrations, and prepared them for printing. At the author&amp;rsquo;s request, we conducted research on references to illustrations that were essential and necessary for the content of the book.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>